<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ls30917_ls30741_ls31293</string>
    <string name="buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="product">Product</string>
    <string name="prize_text">Total price: </string>
    <string name="prize_example">99€</string>
    <string name="see_product">Show</string>
    <string name="add_cart">Add to cart</string>
    <string name="password"> Password </string>
    <string name="informacion"> Basic information</string>
    <string name="enter"> Enter</string>
    <string name="appName"> AndroShopping</string>
    <string name="descripcion">Description: </string>
    <string name="productInfo"></string>
    <string name="show">Show product</string>
    <string name="product_added">added to the cart</string>
    <string name="xbox_description">The Xbox is a home video game console and the first installment
        in the Xbox series of consoles manufactured by Microsoft. It was released on November 15,
        2001 in North America, followed by Australia, Europe and Japan in 2002. It was Microsoft
        first foray into the gaming console market. It is a sixth generation console, and competed with
        Sony's PlayStation 2 and Nintendo's GameCube. It was also the first console produced by an
        American company since the Atari Jaguar ceased production in 1996.</string>
    <string name="sony_description">PlayStation 4 (PS4) is an eighth-generation home video game console
        developed by Sony Interactive Entertainment. Announced as the successor to the PlayStation 3 during
        a press conference on February 20, 2013, it was launched on November 15 in North America, November 29
        in Europe, South America and Australia; and February 22, 2014, in Japan. It competes with Nintendo's
        Wii U and Switch, and Microsoft's Xbox One.</string>
    <string name="mac_description">It’s razor thin, feather light, and even faster and more powerful than before.
        It has the brightest, most colorful Mac notebook display ever. And it features the Touch Bar —
        a Multi-Touch enabled strip of glass built into the keyboard for instant access to the tools you want,
        right when you want them. MacBook Pro is built on groundbreaking ideas. And it’s ready for yours.</string>
    <string name="acer_description">AThe Acer neoTouch P400 is a smartphone designed by Acer Inc. After using Android
        on phones such as the Acer beTouch E110 and Liquid A1, Acer has returned to Microsoft’s operating system.
        It shares the hardware and design with the Acer beTouch E400 but it runs Microsoft Windows Mobile 6.5.3
        operating system, that brings a more finger-friendly user interface. The neoTouch P400 was first introduced
        at the Mobile World Congress 2010 in Barcelona.</string>
    <string name="nexus_description">The Nexus 4 is a smartphone co-developed by Google and LG Electronics that runs
        the Android operating system. It is the fourth smartphone in the Google Nexus product family, unveiled on
        October 29, 2012, and released on November 13, 2012, and succeeded the Samsung-manufactured Galaxy Nexus.
        As with other Nexus devices, the Nexus 4 was sold unlocked through Google Play, but was also retailed by
        wireless carriers.</string>
    <string name="iPad_description">The fourth-generation iPad (marketed as iPad with Retina display, colloquially
        referred to as the iPad 4) is a tablet computer produced and marketed by Apple Inc. Compared to its predecessor,
        the third-generation iPad, the fourth-generation iPad maintained the Retina Display but featured new and upgraded
        components such as the Apple A6X chip and the Lightning connector, which was introduced on September 12, 2012.
        It shipped with iOS 6.0, which provides a platform for audio-visual media, including electronic books, periodicals,
        films, music, computer games, presentations and web content. Like the iPad 2 and the third-generation iPad, it has
        been supported by five major iOS releases, in this case iOS 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10. iOS 11, which was released on 19
        September 2017, does not have support for the fourth-generation iPad because of hardware limitations.</string>
    <string name="authentication">Autentication</string>
    <string name="email"> Email</string>
    <string name="enter_email"> Enter email</string>
    <string name="enter_password"> Enter password</string>
    <string name="enter_uppercase"> ENTER</string>
    <string name="information"> Basic information</string>
    <string name="enter_lowercase"> enter</string>
    <string name="splash_name"> AndroShopping</string>
    <string name="description">Description: </string>
    <string name="product_info"></string>
    <string name="summary"> Purchase summary</string>
    <string name="quantity"> Q:</string>
    <string name="number"> 1 </string>
    <string name="accumulated"> 100€</string>
    <string name="total_prize"> Total Price:  </string>
    <string name="total"> 400€ </string>
    <string name="accept"> Accept </string>
    <string name="success_buy">Shopping success</string>
</resources>
